[Music]
hi everyone welcome back to the channel
today's video is another ample hills one
this is hopelessly devoted to moo and
what is it it's a malted vanilla ice
cream with brooklyn blackout cake and a
pudding swirl
so stick with us and we'll show you how
to make it
[Music]
so this is
walt the cow
hopelessly devoted
to moo
[Music]
i'm sure olivia newton john
probably enjoys this flavor who knows
she probably doesn't even know exists
let's get some of this scooped up so we
can see what this looks like in here
shall we
[Music]
and there we go i mean you can see all
the puddings swirl you can see the
chunks of cake in there this is the
what's left of the cake i'm gonna eat
that whole thing after the video is
finished maybe with some ice cream it's
sunday morning it's kind of what i do so
let's dig into the ice cream now and see
what it tastes like
[Music]
the malted vanilla ice cream is really
nice really nice now i made a malted
ice cream before and i used a different
malt powder i mean you could go probably
even heavier with the malt flavoring if
you use something for brewing but
i didn't want to buy something specific
just for that so
horlicks sachets that's what i used here
and it's given a really nice flavor
really nice flavor
the chocolate cake
it really does just taste like cake
what this tastes like independently is
what it tastes like in there it goes
quite hard gotta say the cake actually
itself goes quite hard
so remember that if you're gonna maybe
over do the simple syrup in the cake
while you're making if that's what you
want to do might help a little bit
but the moment you put it in your mouth
it all softens and breaks up anyway so
it's all good
the pudding slash custard that people
describe for this frosting here works
really well in the ice cream again it
freezes it's not hard but on the harder
side but again once you spoon it put it
in your mouth or just melt straight away
anyway
it's a really nice combo there's a lot
going into this ice cream though the hut
the fact of making an entire cake
and chocolate pudding and then freezing
it ahead of time making the ice cream
there's a lot involved
go and buy a chocolate cake
and then you're good to go then you've
only got to make the chocolate pudding
or the custard for for the add in just
makes this flavor a lot easier ample
heels have nailed this flavor
it's a really nice combo but there's an
awful lot to it would i make it again
absolutely absolutely really nice flavor
really nice combo i hope you give this
one a try let us know how it goes don't
forget to like and subscribe
75 of our viewers are not subscribed to
the channel so make sure you click that
down below help us out and we'll see you
next week
[Music]
you